# Michael Fourie

Nelspruit, Mpumalanga, South Africa

michaelfourie115588@gmail.com

0736656727

linkedin.com/in/michaelfourie158

## Summary

Final Year BSc Information Technology Student @ NWU.

I am an enthusiastic IT student with a passion for technology and the advancements made in technology. I like solving problems. While completing my BSc IT degree, I've gained experience working solo and collaborating in groups with other students working on various projects.

## **Experience**



### 📵 Student Assistant - CMPG 222

North-West University / Noordwes-Universiteit

Jul 2024 - Present (2 months)

Student Assistant (Demi) for the module CMPG 222: Data Analytics.

#### Tasks:

- Marking weekly Tests and Assignments.
- Invigilating written test sessions.
- Assisting the lecturer where I can.

## 🕠 Student Assistant - CMPG 121

North-West University / Noordwes-Universiteit

Jul 2024 - Present (2 months)

Student Assistant (Demi) for the module CMPG 121: C++ Structured Programming.

#### Tasks:

- Marking Weekly Practical Assignments.
- Assisting students with assignments if needed.
- Invigilating written test sessions.
- Assisting the lecturer where I can.

## Functional Tester

#### uTest

Dec 2023 - Present (9 months)

Testing mobile, web, desktop and other (like Android TV) applications.

Bronze rated Tester.

#### Completed:

- 45 Test Cycles
- 22 Test Cases

- 34 Issues reported

Have done software testing for 20 companies, including 3 Fortune 500 companies, and a leading organisation in the motorsports industry.

Won "Academy Tester of the Week" - January 22, 2024

#### **Innibos Ticket Sales**

Innibos

Jun 2024 - Jun 2024 (1 month)

On-site ticket sales using TicketPro systems for the 3 day Innibos Festival.

## Student Assistant - CMPG 214

North-West University / Noordwes-Universiteit

Feb 2024 - Jun 2024 (5 months)

Student Assistant (Demi) for the module CMPG 214: IT Communication Skills.

#### Tasks:

- Marking weekly Tests and Assignments.
- Invigilating written test sessions.
- Assisting the lecturer where I can.

#### **Innibos Ticket Sales**

Innibos

Jun 2023 - Jul 2023 (2 months)

Sold tickets on site using Computicket systems for the 3 day Innibos event.

### **Education**



#### North-West University / Noordwes-Universiteit

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology

Feb 2022 - Nov 2024

#### Skills

```
Python (Programming Language) • HTML • C# • Java • C++ • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) •
SQL • GitHub • JavaScript • Sales
```

### **Honors & Awards**

#### Golden Key Award - Golden Key International Honour Society

Invited to be a member of the Golden Key International Honour Society. Meaning I am in the top 15% of my class.